<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<schemalist gettext-domain="nxdumpclient">
  <schema id="org.v1993.NXDumpClient" path="/org/v1993/NXDumpClient/">
    <key name="dump-path" type="ay">
      <default>b""</default>
      <summary>Path to the output folder</summary>
      <description>
        Path to the directory where dumps are stored.
        Empty value corresponds to using default path.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="flatten-output" type="b">
      <default>false</default>
      <summary>Output directly into dump destination directory</summary>
      <description>
        By default, subfolders are always created when requested by nxdumptool.
        This options forces nxdumpclient to always output single-file dumps into
        dump directory and reduces nesting for multi-file dumps.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="nca-checksum-mode" type="u">
      <range min="0" max="2"/>
      <default>0</default>
      <summary>Checksum verification mode for NCA/NSP files (enumeration)</summary>
      <description>
        (0) Compatible mode parses NSP header, which makes it work with non-standard dump options but delays verification until the end and disables it for standalone NCAs.
        (1) Strict mode takes checksums from NCA filenames, which allows to abort dump early in case of a mismatch.
        (2) None disables checksum verification completely.
        Yes, I know that GSettings support real enumerations, but they are more annoying to use and provide little benefit in my case.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="prompted-for-udev-rules" type="b">
      <default>false</default>
      <summary>Has user closed udev rules prompt</summary>
      <description>
        This is only used in cases where udev rules must me manually installed.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="allow-background" type="b">
      <default>false</default>
      <summary>If application should continue running in background without a window</summary>
      <description>
        Desktop notifications are used to communicate status in this case. Pass `--background` when this option is enabled
        to launch without a window.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="autostart-enabled" type="b">
      <default>false</default>
      <summary>Status of application's autostart capability</summary>
      <description>
        If application is expected to be launched at boot.
        Modifying this option manually will do nothing but confuse the application.
      </description>
    </key>
	</schema>
</schemalist>
